Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Computer Research in Music and Acoustics, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records
  - WERGO Selection letters
    - DECOUST, Michel, "Interphone" CD IV (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - DELIO, Thomas, "Against the Silence" CD IX (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - DODGE, Charles, "Roundelay" CD IV (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - DODGE, Charles, "Any Resemblance is…" CD XI (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - FULTON, Douglas, "Bowling for Blood CD XI (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - GHENT, Manny, "Phosphones" CD II (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - GOEBEL, Johannes, "Of crossing the river" CD III (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - HAYNES, Stanley, "Prisms" CD VIII (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - HARVEY, Jonathan, "Mortuos Plango" CD V (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - JONES, David Evan, "Scritto" CD IV (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - KARPEN, Richard, "Eclipse" CD III (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - KAPEN, Richard, "Exchange" CD- Plus Flute (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - KARPEN, Richard, "II Nome" CD VII (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - KESSLER, Thomas, "Flute Control" CD VI (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - KOENING, G.M., "Three Asko Pieces" CD II (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - KRUPOWICZ, Stanislaw, "Farewell Variations…" CD XI (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - LANSKY, PAUL, "As it Grew Dark" CD XI (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - LINDWALL, Crister, "Points" CD I (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - LORRAIN, Denis, "black it stood as night" CD II (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - LOY, Gareth, "Nekya" CD V (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - MAIGUASHCA, Mesias, "Fmelodies" CD V (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - MOTZ, Wolfgang "Sotto Pressione" CD X (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - NELSON, Gary, "Fractal mountains" CD X (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - OPPENHEIM, Daniel, "Purgatory" CD I (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - PETERSEN, Tracy, "Digital Tantra I" CD VII (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - RAI, Takayuki, "Five Inventions Accompanied by computers" CD VIII (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - REYNOLDS, Roger, "Vanity of Words" CD IV (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - RISSET, Jean-Claude, "L'autre face" CD VII (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - RUSH, Loren, "Little Traveling Music" CD II (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - SAARIAHO, Kaija, "Jardin Secret I" CD V (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - SAVOURET, Alain, "Don Quichotte Company" CD I (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Schottsstaedt, Bill, "Leviathan" CD III (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - SMALLEY, Denis, "Wind Chimes" CD V (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - SMALLEY, Denis, "Clarinet Threads" CD VI (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - STROPPA, Marco, "Traiettoria" CD X (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - TEITLELBAUM, Richard, "Run Some by You" CD VIII (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - TERUGGI, Daniel, "E cosi via" CD VIII (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - VAGGIONE, Horatio, "Thema" CD VI (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - VINAD, Alejandro, "Toccata del Maga" CD XI (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - WESSEL, David, "Antony" CD X (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - WHITE, Frances, "Ogni Rensiero Vola" CD VII (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - WISHART, Trevor, "VOX-5" CD IV (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - WOLMAN, Amnon, "A Circle in the Fire" CD VI (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - YUASA, Yogi, "Towards the Midnight Sun, CD IX (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - YUASA, Joji, "A Study in White" CD VII (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Ensemble Intercontemporain Paris, France WERGO CD #12 - Contract (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Miscellaneous Recording Projects
    - 1983-1984 "The Digital Domain" CD; memos, reviews (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - 1988 Berger/Morrill CD (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - CCRMA Cassette Series I, II, III 1990-1991 Mattox letter-contacts (lists) (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - SDF Tapes (Beta copies) (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - String Quartet CD Centaur Records 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Seamus-April 1993- Tape Concert Series Avaliable (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - LANCINO "Aloni" permissions
    - Aloni-Lancino (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Stanford- Computer Science Reports, 1965, 1981
    - Forsythe, George "Stanford University Program in Computer Science" Tech. Report 1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Masinter, Larry "Interlisp - VAX; a report" Department of Computer Science, Stanford University 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Programs Support CCRMA / Music
    - Course and Degress Bulletin Musci 1980-81 and Poster (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Faculty of the Department of Music at Stanford 1980-81 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Kuhn's CAI-System: Music Teaching Tools 1982; paper and article (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Music at Staford" Newsletter Dec. 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - J. Chowning request for chairs (letter) 1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Take Five- Jazz Newsletters (2) 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Fine Arts Orientation- plans for September 26, 27, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Humans, Animals, Machines: Boundaries and Projections April 23-25. 1987 Green Library- Stanford University (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Continuing Studies offers Computer Music Intro; Spring, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Casper Inaugural 1992; CCRMA participates (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Support OTL etc
    - Stanford Research Policy (also registration booklets for copywriting music); 1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Sony- acoustic research proposal 1986- Physical Modeling Collaboration (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - University Lecture Fund 1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - OTL Director resigns (Campus Report); about OTL (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - OTL proposal- Cook, Gillspee, M. Mathews; letters, etc. 1991-94 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Brent's project- Equipment Donation from Delta Tau 1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Master's Degree Program 1992- (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Perry R. Cook Proposals 1992 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Ear training- Bing Proj, Paul von Hippel (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Sondius ™ news article Oct. 1994 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Research Incentive Grans (OTL) 1994-95 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - OTL Report- Statistics for Joe Koepnick Sept 1994 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - OTL grant application- Smith- December 1994 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - JOS- Research Grant Proposal February 1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - OTL brochures (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Patents, licenses, agreements
    - San Francisco Chronical- Stanford patents April 25, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Stanford IRS nonprofit letter copies; Feb. 1927 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Stanford- Licensed software (compilation) software licensing policy 1983-84 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - 1985 memo-Xerox, Dandy tigers, NEXT machines collaboration between Xerox and CCRMA (and CSLI) (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - 1987 Max Matthews' AT&T system; 11/1987 Acoustic Workstation-Invention, handwritten (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - MIDI Trumpet- 1989 Cook and Morrill (photo)- Stanford-Invention and Technology Disclosure (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Cook-1990 Voice modeling news articles (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Cook- SPASM 1990- Stanford University Invention and Technology Disclosure (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Acoustic Mouse 1990 Matthews Stanford Invention and Technology Disclosure (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Boie drum and electonic pickup - Matthews- patent royalty sharing agreement (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Biomuse 1991 (OTL- Royalties for patent) (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Parcplce license 1991 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Julius Smith-waveguide technology licensed to 2 businesses waveguide 1992 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - 1992 Music Kit- Software Licensing Agreement and related documents (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Carte developpee autdur de l'environment NEXT - IRCAM-CCRMA vaudenteede 1992-1996 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Perry Cook, Julius Smith-Pitch tracking U.S. Patent 1994 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Royalties-license agreement for 'DMIX' (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Yamaha-Original documents
    - FM patent-Yamaha dedication (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Yamaha (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Yamaha- proposal for endowment and computer lab, 1988
    - Yamaha- 1988 proposal for endowment and computer lab (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Yamaha [1]
    - Yamaha books (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Yamaha general correspondence 1978- (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Yamaha disk clavier 1991- (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Yamaha- piano request (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Yamaha studio (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Yamaha GSI (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Yamaha [2]
    - News-Yamaha patent-John Chowning-The Stanford Observer (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Yamaha Patent (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Patents (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Yamaha "Gear" (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Patent Agreements (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Yamaha waveguide (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Yamaha publicity (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Yamaha stuff on loan for Summer workshops 1986 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - J. Chowning- Misc. letters
    - NSF-Request to review proposal (no date) (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - letter from Satoshi Sumitani 3/30/1981 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - J. Chowning- Interviews
    - John Chowning interview with Johannes Goebel June 1978 in German (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Stanford news service-July 1982 John Chowning interview with Julia Sommer (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - John Chowning Interview with Curt Roads 1983 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Yale- John Chowning interview with Vincent Plush- taped May, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - E and MM- 1985 "Techtalk" Chowning interview by Simon Trask (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - John Chowning programs, press clippings, concert reviews
    - John Chowning programs, press clippings, concert reviews [1 of 2] (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - John Chowning programs, press clippings, concert reviews [2 of 2] (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - John Chowning personal file (press clips, review)
    - John Chowning personal file (press clips, review) (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - John Chowning miscellaneous paraphernalia
    - John Chowning: American Academy of Arts and Sciences; 1988- (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - John Chowning: Osgood Hooker Chair April 1992 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - John Chowning listed in encyclopedias,etc. (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - John Chowning lectures, demos, concerts 1990, 1991 a Stanford University and elsewhere (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - John Chowning SEAMUS award for 1993 University of Texasm Austin 3/31/2993 to 4/3/1993 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - John Chowning's Chron. File 1/1/1993-12/31/1993 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Concerts
    - 1967-1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 1994-2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Art-Music collaborations
    - Concert Collaboration - SJSU etc. Fall 1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Bourges
    - Bourges-Awards 1973-1982 (plus correspondence) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Program-XVIIe Festivale International de Musique Experimentale Bourges (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 16th International Electroacoustic Music Competion, Bourges-1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - CCRMA/Italy
    - John Chowning-Paper in Italian (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - CNMAT/CCRMA Berkeley
    - Joint Societies Computer Music Concert (CNMAT and CCRMA) 10 Nov. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Buenos Aires LIPM
    - Concerts Sept. 1986, 1987, 1988 (letters, contracts, etc.) Buenos Aires, Argentina (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - D. Jaffe, "report from Argentina" on bulletin board, Oct. 1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Radio Broadcasts-Buenos Aires 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Argentina concerts March 1990 and 1991-Rockefeller support (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Richardo dal Farra, Argentina: Una Vista al CCRMA 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - CCRMA/France (historical)
    - Le Monde: Oevres pour Ordinateur au G.R.M., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Compagnie Renaud-Barault August/October 1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Communique and reply a Professor Cohen/IRCAM 1974 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Festival D'Automne a Paris, 23 Oct. 1974, Chowning (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - 1970s pamphlet- IRCAM/CCRMA (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Stanford's Musical Marriage, Oakland Tribune, 12 Jan. 1975 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Creation Musicals at Oridinateurs, 21 Mar. 1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Festival D'Anjou. June/July 1975 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Stanford Paris Connection August 1975-Pictures of Boules and Berio with John Leland (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - The New York Times: 8 Aug. 1975, Computer New Field to Boulez (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - San Francisco Chronicle- 9 Aug. 1975, "Something Special in a Concert Hall" (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Computer Rplacing Pen, Keyboard-Boulez Visit, Stanford Daily, 9 Oct. 1975 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Sessions IRCAM-Bruxelles/Grenoble Oct./Nov/ 1975 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Les Principaux Responsables de L'IRCAM, IRCAM visit 1975 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - The New York Times: 27 Feb. 1977, CCRMA Sets example for IRCAM and others (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - San Mateo Times: 26 March 1977, "Paris Invites Stanford Composer" (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - IRCAM Symposium sure la Psychocoustique musicale 11/13 Juillet 1977 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - IRCAM Le compositeur et l'ordinateur 17/21 Feb. 1981, Chowning and McNabb (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Casta Diva par M. Bejart a IRCAM March 1980: Poster in Portfolio (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - IRCAM Ensemble Session 1980/1981 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Articles from Le Monde- 1982 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - IRCAM-misc, 1984-1990 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - IRCAM news
    - Article: Boulez in Paris, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - TIME magazine on IRCAM, Boulez, Oct. 1978 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Boulez, Computer and Music, New York Times, 7 Jan. 1980, Tod Machover at IRCAM (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - May 23-25, 1984 IRCAM: George Lewis Rainbow Family (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - TWA Ambassador June 1984, IRCAM Music and Technology in Concert (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - IRCAM/Boulez, misc.
    - IRCAM: Institut de Recherche et de Coordination Acoustique/Musique (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - IRCAM (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Catgut Acoustical Society, 1991-1994
    - Catgut Acoustical Society: business material, background information (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - CAS Journal, Vol. 1 No. 6, Nov. 1990 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Proposals, Agreements to store CAS Archives at CCRMA (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Presentations- Talks/Demos
    - Colloquium Series, Harvard University, 4 Nov 1982 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Physics Colloquium, Muscial Arts Center, John Chowning, 13 April 1983, location not identified) (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - CCRMA demonstration of computer music 21 Apr. 1983 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - University of Iowa Douglass Fulton Talk, 28 Aug. 1985 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Music Library Association CCARH, Northern California Chapter, Fall Meeting- 14 Nov. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - New York Times 16 Nov. 1986, Merkin Hall, Piano and Yamaha DX7 concert, Chowning on panel (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Pandora's Box: Computers in everyday life, The Brown Symposium, 25-27 March 1987, Southwestern University-Georgetown, Texas (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - University of Chicago Department of Music, FM/MIDI Seminar, July 1987, J. Chowning-guest lecturer (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Acoustical Society Presentation 24 May, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Bartok Seminar and Festival, Hungary 1988, Chowning talk, Risset (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - John Pierce talk on Computers, Music, and Science (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - "The Microtonal Music of Carillo, Mavaro, and Salinas" 23 Feb. 1990? Lecture/Demo: Arturo Salinas at CCRMA (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - "Computer in Musciology", CCRMA 10 March 1990-sponsered by American Musicological Society (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Coll.Mod.Phys./Gren.90, Grenoble, Francec, Lecture/Demos: Chafe, Cook. J. Smith (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Daniel Oppenheim, Nov. 1990, CCRMA, Demonstrats DMIX at Music Meeting at Apple Computer (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Iona College, John Chowning, 9 April 1991 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Audio Engineering Society, Boston, John Chowning's talk, May 1991 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Man-Machine Interacation in live performance- 7,8 June 1991, International Workshop: Pisa, Italy, Andy Scloss, Radio-Drum (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Thanks for giving Audio Engineering Society Tour at their November Conference, San Francisco, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - CCRMA Associates/Affiliates
    - The Associates Program at CCRMA (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Dr. Gordon Bell (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - CCRMA Associates/Affiliates, May 1990 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - CCRMA Associates, May 2000, Abstracts, Open House schedule (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Getty Symposium miscellaneous documents, 1992
    - Getty Symposium 1992 miscellaneous documents (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Getty Symposium financial, administrative correspondence [1 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Getty Symposium financial, administrative correspondence [2 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Getty Symposium financial, administrative correspondence [3 of 3] (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Getty Symposium flyers, programs, 1992
    - Getty Symposium Kresge Auditorium Ja. 1992, Music Publishing an Music Representation in the Technological Age (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Miscellaneous Computer Music Events and Activities
    - International Music and Technology Conference-24-28 Aug. 1981, Melbourne, Australia (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - UCSD Contemporary Music Festival 1981 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - CIRCA, Avignon 1983 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Electronic Art Center of Tokyo, July 1983 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Almeida International Festival of Contemporary Music and Performance 8 June to 8 July to 4 Aug. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Synthese XVIeMe Festivale International de Musique Experinmental, Bourges, 15 June to 4 Aug. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - International Computer Music Conference, 20-24 Oct. 1986, Royal Conservatory, The Hague, Netherlands (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Festivale D'Automne, 1986, Paris (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Swiss Center for Computer Music (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Seventh Almeida International Festival of Contemporary Music and Performance, featuring Ligeti and others, 3 June to 3 July 1987 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Contemporary Arts in Ireland, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Article on New Computer Music Facility in New Haven (Yale) and Jonathan Berger (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Darstadt, Germany, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Interface, 20 Years, 28 Sept. 1991 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Computer Music, 4 April 1992, Chowning, Chafe, Moreno attended (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - International Virtual Reality Project 1993 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Visitors
    - Miscellaneous visitors (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Wayne Slawson, 1978-79 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Visitors 1983-86 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Irmfried Radauer, SDR 10/18/92 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Slonimsky (Nicolas) visited 1994 or 1995 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Theremin, Leon
    - Theremin's Rhythmicon (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - Leon Theremin and Max V. Mathews (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Keyboard Feb. 1992 (Theremin) (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Ligeti, Gyorgy
    - General correspondence with Ligeti and Louise (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Ligeti visit 1993 (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - JC - visit to Ligeti, fall 1988 and Ligeti correspondence (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - News clippings
    - CCRMA; Stanford pubs on CCRMAI; Music; Max Matthews Radio-baton; Leland Smith SCORE (Box 11)
    - Reviews (Concert, CD, book); Commentary (Computer music, contemporary music); Stanford-general news (Box 12)
  - CCRMAI; Music Dept. Misc. (includes Centennial materials) (Box 12)
  - Computers and the Arts (Box 12)
  - Brochures (Box 12)
  - CCRMA Histories and Timeline
    - CCRMA Histories and Timeline (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - CCRMA/BSO 1980 Timelines/histories of organizations (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Stanford News Service-On CCRMA pre-concert publicity 7/1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Historical Artifacts
    - Bell Labs Rec. "the Vocoder" December, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - August 19779 DCR Newsletter No. 148-Nine Months of Labour at Sail (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Historical Artifacts (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Audio Engineering Society 34th Convention 4/29-5/2/1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - USEMUS Manual, 1977 Nov
    - USEMUS November 1977 Manual (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Old Photos scanned at CCRMA
    - Old Photos (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Melba, IMTC Photos of Risset, Chowning 1981 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Patty Wood 5-35-73, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - People at CCRMA miscellaneous info, memos
    - July 10, 1985 Palo Alto Weekly: "Young Composer Pursues a Career" [Bill Susman] (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - CCRMA Roster-1979 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - CCRMA Correspondence
    - CCRMA-Internal Memos, misc. 1985 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - D. Jaffe on South American music scene posed on bulletin board-October 1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Good Sound Foundation-Loren Rush (and NEA proposal-draft) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Historical Memos-Facility Expenses and Receipts
    - Patte's log (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - 1979 Facility-DC Power Lab, Expenses, Letter, and Map (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Concert -receipts and expenses 1980-1984 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - CCRMA Overviews, 1977-1994
    - CCRMA overview 1977 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - CCRMA overview 1979 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - CCRMA overview 1982, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - CCRMA overview 1983-1984, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - CCRMA overviews 1986, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - CCRMA overview 1988 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - CCRMA overviews 1990, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Preparatory Materials for 1994 Overview (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - 1994 Large Overview (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Lists of Compositions Realized at CCRMA
    - CCRMA Tape Catalog (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - CCRMA Compositions 1968-1990 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Lists of Publications (Research Papers) and Sales
    - List of Publications (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - MIT-blanket order with us (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Early Summer Workshops
    - Computer Generated Music Workshop-summer class at Stanford June 23-July 18, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - CCRMA Summer Workshop Announcement 1980-Bulltein (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Summer Workshop, 1982
    - Summer Workshop 1982 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Summer Workshop 1981-1982 Applicants and Faculty (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Summer Workshop, 1983
    - Summer Workshop 1983 [1 of 2] (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Summer Workshop 1983 [2 of 2] (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Summer Workshop Materials, 1984
    - Summer Workshop Materials 1984 [1 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Summer Workshop Materials 1984 [2 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Summer Workshop Materials 1984 [3 of 3] (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Summer Workshop Files, 1986-1990
    - Summer Workshop 1986 (1) Small Advanced Systems, 11 people, 6/23-74 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Summer Workshop 1986 Music Printing on Small Computers, 3 people, 7/7-7-18 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Summer Workshop 1986 (2) Small Advanced Systems, 13 people, 7/7-7/18 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - 1988 Summer Workshops Inquiries (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - CCRMA Summer Workshop 1988 MIDI-Based Synthesis and Composition June 21-July 15, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - CCRMA Summer Workshop 1988 Synthesis and Composition on a large Computer June 21-July 15, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - CCRMA Summer Workshop 1988 Music Printing on Personal Computers July 5-July 15, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Summer Workshops 1988 Administrative Matters (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - CCRMA Summer Workshops 1986 Administrative Matters (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Various SU groups here at CCRMA 1988-1994 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Summer Workshop Brochure 1997 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Computer Music Associations, Historical
    - EMAS newsletters, July 1981, October 1981 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - October 1977 Computer Music Conference, Tentative Schedule (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Computer Music Assocation-Historical/ Newsletters (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Computer Music studios, 1960s
    - Report on Computer Music Studio in Utrecht, May 1968 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Studios, 1970s, 1980s
    - University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Directions Newsletter, UCSD, December 1979 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - CARL (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - University of Victoria, British Colombia, Canada, Software/hardware systems, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - University of Melbourne, Australia, Project 1981 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - ACROE-Studio Brochure (in Grenoble) 1982 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - GRM (Box 13, Folder 63)